So now let's talk about
Bây giờ hãy nói về
the AWS App Runner service.
dịch vụ AWS App Runner.
It's a fully managed service that makes it easy to deploy
Đây là dịch vụ fully managed giúp triển khai dễ dàng
web applications and APIs at scale
ứng dụng web và API ở quy mô lớn
and with this, anyone can deploy to AWS.
và với nó ai cũng có thể triển khai lên AWS.
You don't need to know anything about infrastructure,
Bạn không cần biết gì về hạ tầng,
for containers or your source code or whatever you want.
container hay source code của mình.
So the idea is that you start with your source code
Ý tưởng là bạn bắt đầu với source code
or a Docker container image
hoặc image Docker
and then you're going to configure the settings.
rồi cấu hình các thiết lập.
So it shows how many VCPS you want,
Bạn chọn số vCPU muốn dùng,
how much memory you want for your containers,
bao nhiêu bộ nhớ cho container,
if you want autoscaling and a few health checks.
có autoscaling và vài health check hay không.
So some basic settings to define your web application
Một số thiết lập cơ bản để định nghĩa ứng dụng web
or your API, and then automatically, that's it,
hoặc API, và sau đó xong,
it will start building
nó sẽ bắt đầu build
and deploying the web app using the App Runner survey.
và deploy ứng dụng bằng App Runner.
So the container will be created and deployed,
Container sẽ được tạo và triển khai,
and then your API or your web app is deployed
và API hoặc web app của bạn được triển khai
and you can access it right away using a URL
và bạn truy cập ngay bằng URL
and so, as you can see, there was no knowledge whatsoever
như bạn thấy, không cần hiểu gì
of what goes on underneath.
về bên dưới.
Underneath, of course, uses the AWS services, but as a user,
Bên dưới tất nhiên dùng các dịch vụ AWS, nhưng với người dùng,
you just don't know about it.
bạn không phải quan tâm.
So it's very quick.
Rất nhanh.
So with App Runner, you get a lot of goodness,
Với App Runner bạn nhận được nhiều lợi ích,
you get automatic scaling, it's highly available,
có tự động mở rộng, độ sẵn sàng cao,
you get load balancing,
có load balancing,
you get encryption and your application,
có mã hóa và ứng dụng của bạn,
your container can also get access to your VPC.
container còn truy cập được VPC.
That means that you can connect to your databases,
Điều đó nghĩa là bạn kết nối được đến database,
your cache, as well as your message queue services.
cache và các dịch vụ message queue.
So the use case for this is to very quickly deploy web apps,
Trường hợp sử dụng là triển khai nhanh web app,
API, microservices, and do rapid production deployment
API, microservices và triển khai production nhanh
with best practices, all using the AWS App Runner service.
theo best practice, tất cả nhờ App Runner.
It's a very simple service.
Đây là dịch vụ rất đơn giản.
It does very simple things, but it's very powerful.
Nó làm những việc đơn giản nhưng rất mạnh.
Okay, that's it, I hope you liked it
Vậy là xong, hy vọng bạn thích
and I will see you in the next lecture.
và hẹn gặp lại ở bài kế tiếp.